<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<resources>
    <string-array name="snark_array">
        <item>Right this way, sir!</item>
        <item>Brah! Grab a brewsky!</item>
        <item>Bitches get stitches!</item>
        <item>Oh my gawd. Did you SEE her shoes?</item>
        <item>Psst. You\'ve got a little thing… hanging from your nose… ya need a Kleenex?</item>
        <item>All work and no play makes Jack a dull boy. All work and no play makes Jack a dull boy.</item>
        <item>I\'m taking you to the station. Where is it?</item>
        <item>When I\'m a walkin\' I strut my stuff… La, la, la... Now it\'s stuck in your head, isn\'t it? :)</item>
        <item>English, motherfucker, do you speak it?</item>
        <item>It could probably get worse than this. Wait - it can always get worse. Shit.</item>
        <item>I don\'t hate people. I just like it better when they\'re not around.</item>
        <item>Always be yourself. Unless you suck.</item>
        <item>Give a man a match and he\'ll be warm for a minute. Set him on fire and he\'ll be warm for the rest of his life.</item>
        <item>Everyone is entitled to be stupid, but some abuse the privilege.</item>
        <item>No, those pants don\'t make your butt look big. Your butt makes your butt look big.</item>
        <item>My parents taught me to be kind, humble, and honest; and to save a metric fuckton of plastic bags under the sink.</item>
        <item>I wish I had a Voodoo doll of myself so I could give it a back rub.</item>
        <item>Wait, wait… I had something for this…. Ummm... nope. Lost it.</item>
        <item>You keep using that word, I do not think it means what you think it means.</item>
        <item>That boy is dumber than a box of rocks.</item>
        <item>99 bottles of beer on the wall, 99 bottles of beer...</item>
        <item>Oh, my, God, Becky, look at her butt. It is so big, she looks like one of those rap guys\' girlfriends.</item>
        <item>Dermatologists Hate Her! She is 51 - looks 25. Click her to learn the truth now!</item>
        <item>Leeeeeeroy Jennnnnnnkins!</item>
        <item>All your tables are belong to us.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>